oh come on in no no no no that's fine I yeah my daughter told me you were gonna bring by that
this book yeah she said it's a good read so yeah no problem you know have a seat you can have a
seat I'll just you know sit it down there because you know how I like to keep things clean and stuff
so hang on hang on darling there was oh my god she asked me to give you a book in return but I
I don't know where I put it I'm so sorry you just tell her that you know I will get it to her as
soon as I can I think I thought I put it I really don't know where I had it on the bed but I just
don't know no I don't know what happened to it I am so sorry honey anyway yeah
like I said I'd like to find it because oh hey hey hey honey we said we weren't
gonna do that anymore come on listen you're running a little bit late if you
been half an hour earlier i was fully clothed and oh well it's it it's my anniversary and i'm going
out with my husband sweetie you know that's why i'm really trying to make my relationship work
with him and you just you should try the same with my daughter like we talked about we really
that was just you can't be touching me like that honey no no no please listen sweetheart
You know I adore you.
And you know, oh my God, you're giving me goosebumps.
No, listen, listen.
We talked about this.
I felt so guilty.
The last few times that you fucked me,
I feel bad mostly for my daughter.
Not my husband.
He's a dick.
But I'm trying to make it work because I don't know what else to do.
And it's my anniversary.
My God.
35 36 years oh my goodness and i just think no no um oh oh oh i really think no no no i don't
think you should be like right there like that because stop it you need to you need to not
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes, I'm wet.
Of course I'm wet.
As soon as I knew that you were coming over, I got wet.
But you just, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, honey.
Please, we said we wouldn't do this anymore.
You said.
Oh.
Oh god, I can feel your breath just breathing on me.
God.
No, no, no.
We talked about how much we both love my daughter.
Oh.
No, please, please, please, please.
Please.
You said.
You said...
Oh, God.
Your mouth feels so good, girl.
You know my husband doesn't do that.
Oh, your tongue on my clip.
You know that makes me crazy, honey.
You really should stop.
We both promise we work on our marriages.
Honey.
No, don't stop.
I don't want you to stop.
I mean, I do.
I don't know what the fuck I want.
You understand?
I don't know what I want.
I just know that it's wrong.
And if my daughter ever found it...
Oh, God.
Your tongue.
Your tongue is so magic.
You're gonna make me cum.
Oh god.
Oh, please don't stop.
Don't you...
Don't you dare stop.
Oh god.
Ah.
Oh.
Slide your fingers in, please.
Oh, feel that cream.
Oh, God.
Oh, you make my pussy dream so much.
Oh, sweetie.
Oh, God.
lick the cream off please oh oh oh oh oh oh oh my god oh my god you know
we said we wouldn't do this again
and I know we love my daughter
and I'm working on making my marriage work
I just
oh god you make me feel
so completely whole
filling in
everything
that I can't get from my husband
but
oh
I need to suck you now
you made my pussy
cream so good i need to cum there now oh i need to cum there i make you feel like you made me feel
oh oh oh oh that's my husband um
yeah I'm ready I'm almost ready I'm almost ready yes darling oh I'm I love
you too I'll see you in just a little bit okay baby
I'm gonna be here soon about 10 minutes oh but it might be faster darling and as
much as I want to take care of you my god I left such a mess on the bed I
I think I need to change my panties.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my goodness.
I need to take this off.
Oh, damn it.
You know what?
He used to love when we were younger, I would go without panties all the time.
It would drive him crazy.
You think I should do that for our anniversary?
Oh, my goodness.
I mean, is that a little bit much?
I feel so bad.
You know, you've become so good.
And I just, you know, I just, oh, oh, oh, hello.
Listen, I told you, my husband's on the way, darling.
You are such a little rascal.
But, you know, that's one thing I really, really loved about you.
Oh, my God.
Will you just fuck me one time?
for old times sake and then we should never do it again please please i oh oh oh oh my goodness
oh oh god you want to give me the anniversary fuck but then we really can't do this anymore
darling you know oh I love my daughter and I love just let's I that's why I
think maybe you should oh no that you oh oh my god I just oh fuck I just love how
your cock feels inside of me. Jeez, it feels so amazing and it's so hard. Oh, oh my god.
Oh, fuck, please fuck me. Just, oh god, sweetie, my husband's on his way, but I love how your
cock feels in me. Oh, he knows I'm always running late, so. Oh, God. You made me cum
with your mouth on my clit. Now make me cum, please. Oh, God, make me cum by fucking me.
oh god oh god please fuck me please fuck me make me cum
i need to cum i need to cum tell me tell me tell me how good my pussy feels
oh oh no no no put it back in don't you don't tease me put it back in
mmm
fuck me good make me cum
I'm so juicy
I know I know I know
there it is there it is
oh there it is
holy fuck
there it is
press
grind it in
oh my god
I wanna make you cum
tell me
where
tell me where you want to cum oh fuck oh fuck you make me crazy you feel all those pussy juices on
your balls fuck grind it grind it grind it you fuck me so good and your cock feels oh it feels
perfect in my sweet oh my sweet hungry little pussy oh god oh god i want to taste it i want
to taste it oh you know how i love sucking your dick out of my mouth oh fuck yes oh god yes
oh
mmm
of course my
baby
mmm
mm
hold up
hmm
mmm
You know I love seeing how much gum you have for me.
I've been eating it up.
Oh, God, I got to go.
I have to go, baby.
Do I have any gum on me?